vldpersonals.com 2010-11-21

# Privacy policy | vldPersonals

This privacy policy governs the manner in which VLD Interactive collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users of the vldpersonals.com website, including, but not limited to, the VLD Interactive client area (collectively referred to as the Site).

**What information do we collect?**

We may collect personally identifiable information from you in a variety of ways, including through online forms for ordering products and services, and other instances where you are invited to volunteer such information, including, but not limited to, when you register on our site, place an order or subscribe to our newsletter. When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information.

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience  
Your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs.
  * To improve our website  
We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.
  * To improve customer service  
Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.
  * To process transactions  
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.
  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature
  * To send periodic emails  
The email address you provide for order processing, will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order. If you decide to opt-in to our mailing list, you will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

**How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or access your personal information.

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes, we use cookies (which are small pieces of information that your browser stores on your computer’s hard drive) to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information, except to provide products or services you’ve requested. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third party links**

Our site may contain links to third party sites. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**Childrens online privacy protection act compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

**Your consent**

By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy.

**Changes to our privacy policy**

From time to time we may make adjustments to this privacy policy. Changes to this policy will be made at our sole discretion. Site’s users are encouraged to check this privacy policy for such changes. Your continued use of this site following changes to this privacy policy constitutes your acceptance of the changes.

**Contacting us**

Any questions about this privacy policy should be addressed to us via our [contact form](http://www.vldinteractive.com/contact/).
